<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Movflix</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="empty_string"></string>

    <string name="name">Muhammad Alfin Ramadhan</string>
    <string name="email">alfinramadhan97@gmail.com</string>

    <string name="movie_title">Judul Film</string>
    <string name="movie_title_year">Tahun</string>
    <string name="movie_title_genre">Genre</string>
    <string name="movie_plot">Plot</string>

    <string-array name="movie_name">
        <item>Madagascar 3: Europes Most Wanted</item>
        <item>The Cotton Club</item>
        <item>The Hobbit: The Desolation of Smaug</item>
        <item>Crocodile Dundee</item>
        <item>Flight</item>
        <item>Ratatouille</item>
        <item>City of God</item>
        <item>Shutter Island</item>
        <item>Inception</item>
        <item>Stardust</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="movie_year">
        <item>2012</item>
        <item>1984</item>
        <item>2013</item>
        <item>1986</item>
        <item>2012</item>
        <item>2007</item>
        <item>2002</item>
        <item>2010</item>
        <item>2010</item>
        <item>2007</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="movie_genre">
        <item>Animation, Adventure, Comedy</item>
        <item>Crime, Drama, Music</item>
        <item>Adventure, Fantasy</item>
        <item>Adventure, Comedy</item>
        <item>Drama, Thriller</item>
        <item>Animation, Comedy, Family</item>
        <item>Crime, Drama</item>
        <item>Mystery, Thriller</item>
        <item>Action, Adventure, Sci-Fi</item>
        <item>Adventure, Family, Fantasy</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="movie_plot">
        <item>The penguins and the chimpanzees leave Africa for Monte Carlo in their modified airplane. When they fail to return, Alex, Marty, Melman, Gloria, King Julien, Maurice, and Mort decide that they should go find them and return to their home at the Central Park Zoo in New York City. They find the penguins and chimpanzees at the Monte Carlo Casino. Chaos ensues, and the animals escape from Captain Chantel DuBois, the head of Monacos Animal Control, who is determined to add Alexs head to her taxidermy collection. When their aircraft crash-lands in France, the animals board a departing circus train. The circus animals—a sea lion named Stefano, a jaguar named Gia, and a tiger named Vitaly—are suspicious of outsiders, so Alex lies about them being American circus animals. The circus is headed for a performance show in Rome, followed by one in London where they hope to impress a promoter in order to get their first American tour. To allay suspicion, the penguins purchase the circus from its human ringmaster with the fortune they gained in Monte Carlo. In Rome, Alex becomes enamored with Gia while Julien falls in love with performing bear Sonya. DuBois chases Julien and Sonya by stealing a motor scooter, but fails to catch them and is arrested. The performance at the Colosseum in Rome is a disaster: the animals acts go awry and they are all chased off by the angry audience, though they escape on the train. Stefano explains to Alex that the circus was once famous and Vitaly was its star, skilfully jumping through ever-smaller hoops. However, an accident during one of his stunts caused him to lose his passion and the entire circus suffered as a result. Alex convinces the circus animals to come up with a new and exciting all-animal act that will restore their former glory. Marty and Stefano find a new passion in being shot out of a cannon, while Melman and Gloria become adept at dancing together on a tightrope. Gia persuades Alex to teach her "Trapeze Americano" and the two begin to fall in love. Meanwhile, DuBois escapes from prison, prints a document with a photo of Alex performing at the Central Park Zoo, and recruits her injured henchmen.In London, Vitaly is afraid of failing again and considers ditching the show, but Alex helps him rediscover his passion. At Alex\'s suggestion, Vitaly lubricates himself with hair conditioner instead of olive oil, and succeeds in jumping through the hoop. The show is a spectacular success, and the promoter signs the circus to a contract. DuBois shows up and the penguins manage to foil her attempt to capture Alex. However, Alex\'s photo on the printed document she was carrying reveals that he, Marty, Melman, and Gloria were zoo animals all along. Feeling betrayed and deceived, the circus animals eject the foursome.After an argument between Julien and Sonya, the zoo and circus animals go their separate ways but arrive in Central Park at the same time. Looking in at their old home, the zoo animals realize how much their adventures have changed them and decide that their true place is with the circus. They are then ambushed by DuBois, but before she can behead Alex, the zoo staff arrive and incorrectly believe that she is returning the missing animals. Julien makes it back to the circus with the news and reconciles with Sonya while Gia and Vitaly convince the others that they should rescue their friends. The zoo animals awaken in their old enclosures, now surrounded by high fences. DuBois is being honored by the zoo staff, but she rejects their reward and secretly loads a poison-filled dart and takes aim at Alex. They are soon saved by the circus animals and together defeat DuBois. Alex and his friends permanently join the circus, and Alex and Gia begin a romantic relationship. As retribution for causing their troubles, the penguins ship DuBois and her henchmen in crates to Madagascar, reminiscent of how the animals were shipped in.</item>
        <item>A musician named Dixie Dwyer begins working with mobsters to advance his career but falls in love with Vera Cicero, the girlfriend of gangland kingpin Dutch Schultz.A dancer from Dixies neighborhood, Sandman Williams, is hired with his brother by The Cotton Club, a jazz club where most of the performers are black and the customers are white. Owney Madden, a mobster, owns the club and runs it with his right-hand man, Frenchy.Dixie becomes a Hollywood film star, thanks to the help of Madden and the mob but angering Schultz. He also continues to see Schultzs gun moll, Vera Cicero, whose new nightclub has been financed by the jealous gangster.In the meantime, Dixies ambitious younger brother Vincent becomes a gangster in Schultzs mob and eventually a public enemy, holding Frenchy as a hostage.Sandman alienates his brother Clay at The Cotton Club by agreeing to perform a solo number there. While the clubs management interferes with Sandmans romantic interest in Lila, a singer, its cruel treatment of the performers leads to an intervention by Harlem criminal "Bumpy" Rhodes on their behalf.Dutch Schultz is violently dealt with by Madden\'s men while Dixie and Sandman perform on The Cotton Club\'s stage.</item>
        <item>Thorin Oakenshield and his company are being pursued by Azog and his Orc party. They are ushered by Gandalf to the nearby home of Beorn, a skin-changer who can take the form of a bear. That night, Azog is summoned to Dol Guldur by the Necromancer, who commands him to marshal his forces for war. Azog delegates the hunt for Thorin to his son Bolg. Beorn escorts the company to the borders of Mirkwood, where Gandalf discovers Black Speech imprinted on an old ruin. This, and a prior request by Galadriel, prompt him to investigate the tombs of the Nazgûl. He warns the company to remain on the path before leaving. Upon entering the forest, they lose their way and are ensnared by giant spiders. Bilbo frees the dwarves with the help of the invisibility ring. However, Bilbo begins to understand its dark influence after he drops the ring and brutally kills a spider to retrieve it.The remaining spiders are killed by the Wood-elves led by Tauriel and Legolas, who capture the Dwarves and bring Thorin before their king, Thranduil. Thorin confronts the king about his neglect of the Dwarves of Erebor following Smaugs attack 60 years earlier and is consequently imprisoned with the other Dwarves. Bilbo, having avoided capture, arranges their escape via empty wine barrels that are sent downstream. They are pursued by the Wood-elves and ambushed by Bolg and his Orc party, engaging in a running three-way battle down the river. The Dwarves are able to escape both groups of pursuers, but Kíli is wounded with a Morgul shaft. Thranduil seals off his kingdom when an Orc captive reveals an evil army is amassing in the south, but Tauriel decides to leave and assist the Dwarves; Legolas goes after her. Meanwhile, Gandalf and Radagast investigate the tombs of the Nazgûl, which they find to be empty.The company is smuggled into Esgaroth by a bargeman called Bard. Thorin promises the Master of Laketown a share of the mountains treasure, and they are given arms and sent off to the mountain. Due to his injury, Kíli is forced to remain behind at Bards home, tended to by Fíli, Óin, and Bofur. Bilbo discovers the hidden entrance in the Lonely Mountain and is sent inside to retrieve the Arkenstone. However, he accidentally awakens Smaug, who reveals his knowledge of both the dwarves plot and the return of Sauron.In Laketown, it is revealed that Bard is a descendant of the last ruler of Dale and possesses the last black arrow capable of killing Smaug. Bard attempts to bring the black arrow to the towns launcher, fearing what may happen in the mountain. However, he is arrested by the Master, charging his son to hide the arrow. Bolg and his Orc party infiltrate the town and attack the four Dwarves, but Tauriel and Legolas arrive and quickly dispatch them.Meanwhile, Gandalf infiltrates Dol Guldur alone after sending Radagast to warn Galadriel of their discovery at the tombs. He finds and cures Thrain before they are ambushed by Azog. The Necromancer overpowers and defeats Gandalf and reveals himself as Sauron. Gandalf watches helplessly as Azog and an Orc army march from Dol Guldur towards the Lonely Mountain.Inside the mountain, during a long chase, Bilbo and the Dwarves rekindle the mountains forge using Smaugs flames and melt a large golden statue, hoping to bury Smaug alive in the molten gold. They do so, but Smaug emerges from the gold, stumbles out of the mountain and flies off to destroy Laketown as Bilbo watches in despair.</item>
        <item>Sue Charlton is a feature writer for her fathers newspaper Newsday, and is dating the editor Richard Mason. She travels to Walkabout Creek, a small township in the Northern Territory of Australia, to meet Michael J. "Crocodile" Dundee, a bushman reported to have lost half a leg to a saltwater crocodile before crawling hundreds of miles to safety. On arrival in Walkabout Creek, she cannot locate Dundee, but she is entertained at the local pub by Dundees business partner Walter "Wally" Reilly. When Dundee arrives that night, Sue finds his leg is not missing, but he has a large scar which he refers to as a "love bite". While Sue dances with Dundee, a group of city kangaroo shooters make fun of Dundees status as a crocodile hunter, causing him to knock the leader out with one punch.At first, Sue finds Dundee less "legendary" than she had been led to believe, unimpressed by his pleasant-mannered but uncouth behaviour and clumsy advances towards her. She is later amazed, when in the outback, she witnesses "Mick" (as Dundee is called) subduing a water buffalo, taking part in an Aboriginal (Pitjantjatjara) tribal dance ceremony, killing a snake with his bare hands, and scaring away the kangaroo shooters by tricking them into thinking one of the kangaroos is shooting back.The next morning, offended by Micks assertion that as a "sheila" she is incapable of surviving the Outback alone, Sue goes out alone to prove him wrong but takes his rifle with her at his request. Mick follows her to make sure she is okay, but when she stops at a billabong to collect water, she is attacked by a large crocodile and is rescued by Mick. Overcome with gratitude, Sue finds herself becoming attracted to him.Sue invites Mick to return with her to New York City on the pretext of continuing the feature story. At first Wally scoffs at her suggestion, but he changes his mind when she tells him the newspaper would cover all expenses. Once in New York, Mick is perplexed by local behaviour and customs but overcomes problematic situations including two encounters with a pimp and two attempted robberies. After this Sue realises her true feelings for him, and they kiss.At a society dinner at her father\'s home in honour of Sue\'s safe return and of Mick\'s visit, Richard proposes marriage to Sue, and in a haze of confused emotions, she initially accepts in spite of Richard having recently revealed his self-centered and insensitive "true colours" during a period of intoxication.Mick, disheartened at Sue\'s engagement, decides to go "walkabout" around the United States, but Sue has a change of heart and, deciding not to marry Richard, follows Mick to a subway station. There, she cannot reach him through the crowd on the platform, but has members of the crowd relay her message to him, whereupon he climbs up to the rafters and walks to Sue on the heads and raised hands of the onlookers and kisses her, to the delight of the crowd, where they receive a round of applause.</item>
        <item>Airline pilot Captain Whip Whitaker uses cocaine to stay alert after a sleepless night in his Orlando hotel room. He pilots SouthJet Flight 227 to Atlanta, which experiences severe turbulence during takeoff. Co-pilot Ken Evans takes over while Whip discreetly mixes vodka in his orange juice and takes a nap. He is jolted awake as the plane goes into a steep dive. Unable to regain control, Whip is forced to make a controlled crash landing in an open field, hitting his head and losing consciousness on impact.Whip awakens in an Atlanta hospital with moderate injuries and is greeted by his old friend Charlie Anderson, who represents the airlines pilots union. He tells Whip that he managed to save 96 out of 102, losing two crew members and four passengers, but mentions his co-pilot is in a coma. Whip sneaks away for a cigarette and meets Nicole Maggen, a heroin addict recovering from an overdose in the same hospital. The next morning, his friend and drug dealer Harling Mays picks him up from the hospital.Having retired to his late fathers farm, Whip meets Charlie and attorney Hugh Lang, who explain that the National Transportation Safety Board (NTSB) performed a drug test while he was unconscious. Results showed that Whip was intoxicated during the flight, although Hugh gets the toxicology report voided on technical grounds. Whip visits and becomes intimate with Nicole, but his drinking habits clash with Nicoles attempts to stay drug-free. Later, he attends a funeral for Katerina, a flight attendant who died in the crash, and with whom Whip had spent the night before the incident. He sees a surviving crew member, Margaret, and asks her to tell the NTSB that he was sober.Whip pays a visit to his co-pilot Ken Evans after he awakens from his coma. Evans has likely lost much of his ability to walk and may never pilot an airplane again. Although upset, Evans has no intention of telling the NTSB that Whip was drinking. Nicole decides to separate from Whip after he fails to stay sober and he spontaneously drives to the home of his ex-wife and son, both of whom resent him. Hounded by the media, he stays with Charlie until the NTSB hearing, vowing not to drink. The night before the hearing, Charlie and Hugh move Whip to a guarded hotel room with no alcohol. He finds the door to an adjacent room unlocked and raids the minibar there.The next morning, Charlie discovers Whip passed out drunk. Whip and Charlie call Harling to provide Whip with cocaine, hoping to get him alert enough to make it through the hearing. At the hearing, lead NTSB investigator Ellen Block explains that a damaged elevator assembly jackscrew was the primary cause of the crash. She commends Whip on his valor and skill, noting that no other pilot was able to land the plane in simulations of the crash. She then reveals that two empty vodka bottles were found in the planes trash, despite beverages not being served to passengers, and that Whips blood test was excluded for technical reasons. She then states the only other member of the crew to test positive for alcohol was Katerina. Whip pauses, unable to bring himself to blame Katerina for his actions. He collects himself and comes clean, admitting to being intoxicated the day of the crash. A tearful Whip also admits that he is presently drunk and has a problem, coming to terms with his alcoholism.Thirteen months later, an imprisoned Whip is lecturing a support group of fellow inmates telling them he is glad to be sober and doesnt regret doing the right thing. He is also working to rebuild his relationship with his son, who visits to interview Whip for a college application essay titled "The most fascinating person that I\'ve never met". He begins by asking, "Who are you?" As a plane flies overhead, Whip replies, "That\'s a good question."</item>
        <item>Remy, a young rat with heightened senses of taste and smell, dreams of becoming a chef like his human idol, the late Auguste Gusteau, but the rest of his colony, including his older brother Émile and his father, the clan leader Django, only eat for sustenance and are wary of humans. The rats live in an elderly womans attic outside Paris, but when the woman discovers them, they are forced to evacuate, and Remy is separated from the others. Encouraged by an imaginary Gusteau, he explores until he finds himself on the roof of Gusteaus restaurant.Remy notices the restaurants new garbage boy, Alfredo Linguini, attempting to fix a soup he ruined, and jumps in to fix Linguinis mistakes. Linguini catches Remy in the act, but does not reveal him to Skinner, Gusteaus former sous-chef and the new owner of the restaurant. Skinner confronts Linguini for tampering with the soup, but when the soup is accidentally served and proves to be a success, Colette Tatou, the restaurants only female chef, convinces Skinner to retain Linguini and uphold Gusteaus motto, "Anyone can cook". After demanding that Linguini replicate the soup, Skinner spots Remy and orders Linguini to take him outside and kill him. Once they are alone, Linguini discovers that Remy can understand him, and he convinces Remy to help him cook.Remy controls Linguinis movements like a marionette by pulling on his hair while hiding under his toque. They recreate the soup, and continue cooking at the restaurant. Colette begrudgingly trains Linguini, but steadily comes to appreciate someone heeding her advice. Later, Remy finds Émile and reunites with the clan. After Remy tells Django that he intends to stay at the restaurant, Django shows him a group of exterminated rats in an attempt to convince him that humans are dangerous, but Remy ignores his warnings and leaves.Meanwhile, Skinner discovers through a letter from Linguinis late mother that Linguini is Gusteaus illegitimate son, and the rightful owner of the restaurant. Skinner is shocked and enraged about this revelation, as Gusteaus will stated that he would inherit ownership of the restaurant, only if no biological heir appeared two years prior to the latters death. After his lawyer verifies that Linguini is Gusteaus heir, Skinner hides the evidence in an envelope, but Remy finds it and runs away, showing the documents to Linguini, who then forces Skinner out. The restaurant thrives as Remys recipes become popular, and Linguinis life improves as he develops a romantic relationship with Colette. Food critic Anton Ego, whose previous negative review of the restaurant indirectly led to Gusteaus death, announces to Linguini that he will dine at the restaurant. After Linguini takes credit for Remys cooking at a press conference, he and Remy have a falling out. As revenge, Remy leads his clan to raid the restaurants pantries for food. Linguini arrives to apologize, but upon discovering the raid, he furiously kicks Remy and the other rats out.The next day, Remy is captured by Skinner but promptly freed by Django and Émile. After returning to the restaurant, he and Linguini reconcile, and Linguini reveals the truth to his staff, who all immediately quit. Reminded of Gusteau\'s motto, Colette returns to help Django and the clan cook to Remy\'s directions, while Linguini waits tables. Skinner and a health inspector attempt to interfere, but are locked in the pantry by the rats. Remy creates a variation of ratatouille which reminds Ego of his mother\'s cooking. Ego asks to meet the chef, and is stunned upon being introduced to Remy after the restaurant closes for the evening. The next day, he writes a review titled "France\'s Finest", stating that he has come to understand Gusteau\'s motto, and describes Remy - without revealing that he is a rat - as "nothing less than the finest chef in France".After Skinner and the health inspector are released, they inform the authorities and the restaurant is shut down, stripping Ego of his job and credibility. Remy, Linguini and Colette open a bistro, called La Ratatouille, which a now-happier Ego invests in and frequently visits; the rat colony settles into the bistro\'s attic as their new home.</item>
        <item>The film begins in medias res with an armed gang chasing after an escaped chicken in a favela called the Cidade de Deus ("City of God"). The chicken stops between the gang and the narrator, a young man nicknamed Rocket ("Buscapé").The film flashes back to the 1960s where the favela is shown as a newly built housing project with few resources. Three impoverished, amateur thieves known as the "Tender Trio" – Shaggy ("Cabeleira"), Clipper ("Alicate"), and Rockets older brother, Goose ("Marreco") – rob business owners and share the money with the community who, in turn, hide them from the police.Lil Dice (Dadinho), a young boy, convinces them to hold up a motel and rob its occupants. The gang resolves not to kill anyone and tells Lil Dice to serve as a lookout. Instead, Lil Dice guns down the motel occupants after falsely warning the trio that the police are coming. The massacre attracts so much police attention that the trio is forced to split up: Clipper joins the Church, Shaggy is shot by the police while trying to escape the favela, and Goose is shot by Lil Dice after taking his money while Lil Dices friend Benny (Bené), Shaggys brother, watches.In the 1970s, the favela has been transformed into an urban jungle. Rocket has joined a group of young hippies. He enjoys photography and likes one girl, Angélica, but his attempt to get close to her is ruined by a gang of petty criminal kids known as "The Runts". Lil Dice, who now calls himself "Li\'l Zé" ("Zé Pequeno"), has established a drug empire with Benny by eliminating all of the competition, except for Carrot, who is a good friend of Bennys.Lil Zé takes over "the apartment", a known drug distribution center, and forces Carrots manager Blacky ("Neguinho"), to work for him instead. Coincidentally, Rocket visits the apartment to get some drugs off Blacky for Angélica during the apartment raid. Through narration, Rocket momentarily considers attempting to kill Lil Zé to avenge his brother but decides against it. He is let go after Benny tells Lil Zé that Rocket is Gooses brother.Later, a relative peace comes over the City of God under the reign of Lil Zé, who manages to avoid police attention. Benny decides to branch out of the drug dealer crowd and befriends Tiago, Angélicas ex-boyfriend, who introduces him to his (and Rockets) friend group. Benny and Angélica begin dating. Together, they decide to leave the City and the drug trade.During Bennys farewell party, Zé and Benny get into an argument. Blacky accidentally kills Benny while trying to shoot Lil Zé. Bennys death leaves Lil Zé unchecked. Carrot kills Blacky for endangering his life. Lil Zé and a group of his soldiers start to make their way to Carrots hideout to kill him.On the way, Zé follows a girl who dismissed his advances at Bennys party. He beats up her boyfriend, a peaceful man named Knockout Ned (Mané Galinha), and rapes her. After Neds brother stabs Lil Zé, his gang retaliates by shooting into his house, killing his brother and uncle in the process. A gang war breaks out between Carrot and Lil Zé. A vengeful Ned sides with Carrot.The war is still ongoing a year later, in 1981, the origin forgotten. Both sides enlist more "soldiers" and Li\'l Zé gives the Runts weapons. One day, Li\'l Zé has Rocket take photos of him and his gang. A reporter publishes the photos, a significant scoop since no outsiders can safely enter the City of God anymore. Rocket believes Li\'l Zé will kill him for publishing the photo of him and his gang. The reporter takes Rocket in for the night, and he loses his virginity to her. Unbeknownst to him, Li\'l Zé, jealous of Ned\'s media fame, is pleased with the photos and with his own increased notoriety.Rocket returns to the City for more photographs, bringing the film back to its opening scene. Rocket finds himself caught between Zé\'s gang and the arriving police, who quickly withdraw when they realize they are outnumbered and outgunned. Rocket is surprised that Zé asks him to take pictures, but as he prepares to take the photo, Carrot\'s gang arrives. In the ensuing gunfight, Ned is killed by a boy who has infiltrated his gang to avenge his father, a policeman whom Ned has shot during a earlier scene involving a bank robbery. The police capture Li\'l Zé and Carrot and plan to show Carrot off to the media. Since Li\'l Zé has been bribing the police, they take all of Li\'l Zé\'s money and let him go, but Rocket secretly photographs the scene. The Runts murder Zé to avenge the Runt murdered at the behest of Zé; they intend to run his criminal enterprise themselves.Rocket contemplates whether to publish the cops\' photo, expose corruption, and become famous, or the picture of Li\'l Zé\'s dead body, which will get him an internship at the newspaper. He decides on the latter, and the film ends with the Runts walking around the City of God, making a hit list of the dealers they plan to kill to take over the drug business.</item>
        <item>In 1954, U.S. Marshal Edward "Teddy" Daniels and his new partner Chuck Aule travel to Ashecliffe Hospital for the criminally insane on Shutter Island, Boston Harbor to investigate the disappearance of Rachel Solando, a patient of the hospital who had previously drowned her three children.The staff, led by psychiatrist Dr. John Cawley, appear uncooperative. The marshals learn that Dr. Lester Sheehan, who was treating Solando, had left the island on vacation immediately after Solando disappeared. Teddy experiences migraine headaches, flashbacks of his experiences as a U.S. Army soldier during the liberation of Dachau, and also vivid dreams of his wife Dolores, who was killed in a fire set by arsonist Andrew Laeddis. Teddy explains to Chuck that he took the case to find Laeddis, believing he is on the island. Solando suddenly resurfaces and believes Teddy is her husband. Teddy later breaks into the restricted Ward C to find Laeddis where he meets patient George Noyce who appears to know him well. He tells Teddy that the doctors are experimenting on patients, some of whom are taken to a lighthouse to be lobotomized. He warns Teddy that everyone is deceiving him and tells him not to trust Chuck.Teddy regroups with Chuck and they climb the cliffs toward the lighthouse but become separated. Believing he saw Chucks body on the rocks below, Teddy climbs down but finds only a cave where a woman claiming to be the real Solando is hiding. She states that she is a former psychiatrist who discovered clandestine experiments to develop mind control but was forcibly committed. She says that Cawley and Dr. Naehring will use Teddys war trauma to feign a psychotic break, allowing them to have him also committed. Teddy returns to the hospital and is greeted by Cawley. When Teddy asks about Chucks whereabouts, Cawley firmly insists that Teddy does not have a partner and that he arrived on the island alone.Convinced Chuck was taken to the lighthouse, Teddy heads there but runs into Naehring, who attempts to sedate him. Teddy overpowers him and breaks into the lighthouse, only to discover Cawley waiting for him. Teddy confronts Cawley and reveals his encounter with Solando, saying he believes Cawley is experimenting on him. Cawley denies that Solando ever existed, and insists that Teddy has not been drugged, explaining the tremors as withdrawals from Chlorpromazine, a neuroleptic medication that Teddy has been taking for two years. Chuck arrives and reveals he is in fact, Dr. Sheehan. Cawley explains that "Teddy" is Andrew Laeddis, a U.S. Marshal incarcerated at Ashecliffe for murdering his manic depressive wife after she drowned their three children. Andrew did not seek treatment for Dolores when she burned down their apartment and instead moved his family to a lake house, where Dolores carried out the killings. Cawley explains that Andrew\'s delusion is a result of his guilt, that his migraines and hallucinations are withdrawal symptoms, and that he had created the alternate persona of Edward Daniels[a], also a Marshal, who acted violently and espoused conspiracy theories about the facility. The "investigation" is an elaborate role-play to regain his true persona. Overwhelmed by his sudden recall, Andrew faints.Awakening later, Andrew calmly recounts the truth, satisfying the doctors that he is lucid. Cawley notes that they had achieved this state nine months before, but that Andrew had quickly regressed. He warns that this will be Andrew\'s last chance and if he lapses again he will be lobotomized due to his very violent conduct towards other patients such as Noyce, and towards the guards. Sometime later, Andrew relaxes on the hospital grounds with Sheehan. Appearing delusional, Andrew again refers to Sheehan as "Chuck" and says they must leave the island. Sheehan signals to Cawley, who orders that Andrew be lobotomized. Andrew then asks Sheehan if it would be worse "to live as a monster, or to die as a good man?" A stunned Sheehan calls Andrew "Teddy" but the latter does not respond and leaves peacefully with the orderlies for his operation.</item>
        <item>Cobb and Arthur are "extractors" who perform corporate espionage using experimental dream-sharing technology to infiltrate their targets subconscious and extract information. Their latest target, Saito, is impressed with Cobbs ability to layer multiple dreams within each other. He offers to hire Cobb for the ostensibly impossible job of implanting an idea into a persons subconscious; performing "inception" on Robert Fischer, the son of Saitos competitor Maurice Fischer, with the idea to dissolve his fathers company. In return, Saito promises to clear Cobbs criminal status, allowing him to return home to his children.Cobb accepts the offer and assembles his team: a forger named Eames, a chemist named Yusuf, and a college student named Ariadne. Ariadne is tasked with designing the dreams architecture, something Cobb himself cannot do for fear of being sabotaged by his minds projection of his late wife Mal. Maurice Fischer dies, and the team sedates Robert Fischer into a three-layer shared dream on an airplane to America bought by Saito. Time on each layer runs slower than the layer above, with one member staying behind on each to perform a music-synchronized "kick" (using the French song "Non, je ne regrette rien") to awaken dreamers on all three levels simultaneously.The team abducts Robert in a city on the first level, but they are attacked by his trained subconscious projections. After Saito is wounded, Cobb reveals that while dying in the dream would normally awaken dreamers, Yusufs sedatives will instead send them into "Limbo": a world of infinite subconscious. Eames impersonates Roberts godfather, Peter Browning, to introduce the idea of an alternate will to dissolve the company.Cobb tells Ariadne that he and Mal entered Limbo while experimenting with dream-sharing, experiencing fifty years in one night due to the time dilation with reality. Mal refused to return to reality, and Cobb instead performed inception on her to convince her. After waking up, Mal still believed she was dreaming. Attempting to "wake up", she committed suicide and framed Cobb to force him to do the same. Cobb fled the U.S., leaving his children behind.Yusuf drives the team around the first level as they are sedated into the second level, a hotel dreamed by Arthur. Cobb persuades Robert that he has been kidnapped by Browning to stop the dissolution and that Cobb is a defensive projection, leading Robert another third level deeper as part of a ruse to enter Robert\'s subconscious.In the third level, the team infiltrates an alpine fortress with a projection of Maurice inside, where the inception itself can be performed. However, Yusuf performs his kick too soon by driving off a bridge, forcing Arthur and Eames to improvise a new set of kicks synchronized with them hitting the water, by rigging an elevator and the fortress respectively with explosives. Mal then appears and kills Robert before he can be subjected to the inception and he and Saito are lost into Limbo, forcing Cobb and Ariadne to rescue them in time for Robert\'s inception and Eames\'s kick. Cobb makes peace with his part in causing Mal\'s death. Ariadne kills Mal\'s projection and wakes Robert up with a kick.Revived into the third level, he discovers the planted idea: his dying father telling him to create something for himself. While Cobb searches for Saito in Limbo, the others ride the synced kicks back to reality. Cobb finds an aged Saito and reminds him of their agreement. The dreamers all awaken on the plane, and Saito makes a phone call. Arriving at L.A., Cobb passes the immigration checkpoint and his father-in-law accompanies him to his home. Cobb uses Mal\'s "totem" – a top that spins indefinitely in a dream – to test if he is indeed in the real world, but he chooses not to observe the result and instead joins his children.</item>
        <item>The English village of Wall lies near a stone wall that borders the magical kingdom of Stormhold. A guard prevents anyone from crossing. Dunstan Thorne tricks him and crosses over the wall to a marketplace. He meets Una, an enslaved princess who offers him a glass snowdrop in exchange for a kiss. They spend the night together. Nine months later, the guard delivers to Dunstan a baby, whose name is Tristan.Eighteen years later, the dying King of Stormhold throws a ruby into the sky: his successor will be the first of his sons to recover it. The gem hits a star, and both fall out of the sky, landing in Stormhold. The princes Primus and Septimus independently search for the stone.In Wall, Tristan and Victoria see the falling star. He vows to retrieve it, in return for her hand in marriage. Despite his mother being from beyond the wall, he cannot get past the guard. He receives a Babylon candle that she left for him, which can take the user to any desired location. Tristan lights it and is transported to the fallen star, personified as a woman named Yvaine. He uses a magic chain to claim her and to take her to Victoria.Three ancient witch sisters resolve to eat the fallen stars heart to recover their youth and replenish their powers. Their leader, Lamia, eats the remnants of an earlier stars heart, and sets off to find Yvaine. She conjures up a wayside inn as a trap.Yvaine becomes tired, so Tristan chains her to a tree and promises to bring food. In his absence, a unicorn releases her, but unwittingly takes her to Lamias inn. Tristan discovers Yvaine gone, but the stars whisper that she is in danger, telling him to get on a passing coach, which happens to be Primus. They stop at the inn, interrupting Lamias attempt to kill Yvaine. Lamia kills Primus, while Tristan and Yvaine use the Babylon candle to escape into the clouds, where they are captured by pirates in a flying ship. The leader, Captain Shakespeare, tells his crew that Tristan is his nephew and Yvaine, a friend. He gives them new clothes, teaches Tristan how to fence and Yvaine how to dance.Septimus, being the last surviving son, only needs to find the stone to claim the throne. He learns Yvaine has it and realizes that her heart grants immortality.After leaving Captain Shakespeare, Tristan and Yvaine confess their love for one another and spend the night together at an inn. Next morning, Tristan leaves Yvaine sleeping and goes with a lock of her hair, to tell Victoria he has fallen in love with Yvaine. When the lock turns to stardust, he realizes Yvaine will die if she crosses the wall, and rushes back to save her.Yvaine finds Tristan gone, and–thinking he has abandoned her for Victoria–despondently walks towards the wall. Una notices Yvaine walking to her doom and takes the reins of Ditchwater Sals caravan to stop her. Lamia kills Sal, and captures Una and Yvaine, taking them to the witches manor. Septimus and Tristan pursue Lamia, agreeing to work together for the time being. Barging into the castle, Septimus recognizes Una as his long-lost sister, and Una tells Tristan that she is his mother.Septimus and Tristan kill two of the witches, but Lamia uses a voodoo doll to kill Septimus. Lamia is about to finish Tristan off, when she appears to break down over the loss of her sisters. Lamia frees Yvaine, but her feigned defeat was a ruse, and she tries to kill them both. As Tristan and Yvaine embrace, their love allows her to shine once again, killing Lamia.Tristan retrieves Yvaines gem, and Una reveals that, as her son, Tristan is the last male heir of Stormhold. He becomes king with Yvaine as his queen, and Dunstan and Una are reunited. After eighty years of rule, they use a Babylon candle to ascend to the sky, where they live together as stars.</item>
    </string-array>



    <string-array name="movie_photo">
        <item>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTM2MTIzNzk2MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMDcwMzQxNw@@._V1_SX300.jpg</item>
        <item>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTU5ODAyNzA4OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNzYwNTIzNA@@._V1_SX300.jpg</item>
        <item>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMzU0NDY0NDEzNV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwOTIxNDU1MDE@._V1_SX300.jpg</item>
        <item>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTg0MTU1MTg4NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDgzNzYxMTE@._V1_SX300.jpg</item>
        <item>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTUxMjI1OTMxNl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNjc3NTY1OA@@._V1_SX300.jpg</item>
        <item>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTMzODU0NTkxMF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMjQ4MzMzMw@@._V1_SX300.jpg</item>
        <item>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjA4ODQ3ODkzNV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTYwOTc4NDI3._V1_SX300.jpg</item>
        <item>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTMxMTIyNzMxMV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwOTc4OTI3Mg@@._V1_SX300.jpg</item>
        <item>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjAxMzY3NjcxNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNTI5OTM0Mw@@._V1_SX300.jpg</item>
        <item>https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjkyMTE1OTYwNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMDIxODYzMw@@._V1_SX300.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>